hello everyone this is e I'm e censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is the 14th of February 2024
wanted to get a quick video out to you
that my latest book on Supernatural
Bible changes is now available on Amazon
I've titled this engines of War riots
and Dragons military and politics
Supernatural Bible changes this book has
over
500 KJV Bible verses that have been
altered with a theme of War riots and
Dragons politics military now dropped
into
scripture and in these verses you're
going to see everything from grammar
errors to nonsense verses to doctrinal
erors to emoticons to new words words
erase new people new countries and on
and on it goes our bibles are under
satanic assault and supernaturally
changing preparing the way for the
Antichrist I'm going to go ahead and
show you um the review on Amazon here it
is right here and our Bibles the King
James Bible specifically now has new
words in it like presidents Senators
Senate artillery Munitions Navy armed
men polling Gaza and so much more many
more new words in the Bible and it's
crazy
so in this book again it's about 9 in by
6 in larger than my smaller books I have
four verses on each page let me go ahead
and show you some of
them starting here 1 Corinthians 97 says
this today who goeth a Warfare anytime
at his own
charges who planteth a Vineyard and
eateth not of the fruit thereof or who
feedeth A Flock and eateth not of the
milk of the flock now as my other books
similar to my other books I'm not
stating what the exact changes are in
each of these verses either you're going
to see them or you don't this one has
new words in it and then obviously
grammar
errors if you have eyes to see like
question mark and the next word has a
small letter grammatically
incorrect and new words Daniel 3:3 says
this today then the princes
the governors and captains the judges
the treasurers the counselors the
sheriffs and all the rulers of the
provinces were gathered together unto
the dedication of the image that
Nebuchadnezzar the king had set up and
they stood before the image that
Nebuchadnezzar had set up do you see the
new words and there's even just grammar
errors here Jeremiah 11:7 for I
earnestly protested unto your fathers in
the day that I brought them up out of
the land of Egypt even into this day
Rising early and protesting saying obey
my
voice this would be the Lord
speaking Matthew 1422 and straight way
Jesus constrained his disciples to get
into a ship and to go before him unto
the other side while he sent the
multitudes away First Kings 101 and the
Navy also of hyam that brought gold from
ofer brought in from ofer great plenty
of almug trees and precious stones
Daniel 62 and over these three
presidents of whom Daniel was first that
the princes might give accounts unto
them and the King should have no
damage Jeremiah 14:6 and the wild asses
did stand in the high places they
snuffed up the wind like
dragons their eyes did fail because
there was no
grass Matthew 14:29 and he said come and
when Peter was come down out of the ship
he walked on the water to go to
Jesus First Kings 10:15 beside that he
had of the merchant men and of the
traffic of the spice merchants and all
the kings of Arabia
and of the governors of the
country Daniel 63 then this Daniel was
preferred above the presidents and
princes because an excellent Spirit was
in him and the King thought to set him
over the whole
realm Jeremiah 2:26 as a thief is
ashamed when he is found so is the house
of Israel ashamed they their kings their
princes and their priests and their
prophets Matthew 14:9 and the King was
sorry nevertheless for the oath sake and
them which sat with him at meat he
commanded it to be given
her and on and on it goes there are many
new verses in Scripture that
literally make zero sense new language
new doctrine new people words omitted
filler words emoticons punctuation
errors and on and on it goes and it's
time to wake up in Jesus name these
books are a tool for anyone who's
researching this topic and wants to have
an easy way to see
them I have several books now available
on Amazon any of them are great tools to
start showing people what is now in
scripture and the changes in my mind are
undeniable many of the verses I just
read to you don't even make
sense and it's not because I don't have
spiritual eyes they literally make no
sense there is gibberish now in our
Bibles across translations across
languages it's time to wake up Church in
Jesus name be strong and courageous
brothers and sisters do not fear or be
dismayed for the Lord your God is with
you wherever you go until next time